repxpert.com 2016-04-06

# Data Protection Information | REPXPERT Site

Thank you for your interest in our company and in our products. Protecting your privacy while using our online services is very important to us. We comply with the legal requirements of the country in which the site processing the data is located when collecting and processing personal data. In the Federal Republic of Germany, the applicable law is the Federal Data Protection Act.

 **Collecting and Processing Personal Data**

When you visit our websites, our web servers save the name of your Internet service provider, the IP address, the website from which you are visiting our site, our sites visited by you, as well as the date and the duration of the visit. This data undergoes statistical analysis. It is not connected to any personal data. We use cookies in order to recognize the preferences of visitors so that we can improve the content of our websites accordingly. Each individual user remains anonymous. Personal details are only saved when you enter them voluntarily in the online services provided.

To ensure the tailored design and optimum performance of this website, solutions and technologies by econda GmbH (www.econda.de) not only collect and store anonymized data, but also utilize this data to compile usage profiles by means of pseudonyms. Cookies can be used for this purpose which make it possible for an Internet browser to be recognized. Without the express consent of a visitor, however, usage profiles will not be stored together with data pertaining to the pseudonymous visitor. IP addresses, in particular, are rendered indecipherable immediately after receipt, which makes it impossible to match a usage profile with an IP address. Visitors to this website can opt out [here](http://www.econda.com/econda/company/data-protection/revocation-of-data-storage/ "here")—at any time—of the collecting and storing of their data.

 **Using and Forwarding Personal Data, Collecting Data for Specific Purposes and Options**

We use the technical data for website administration purposes. This means we use your personal data to manage customers and those generally interested in the company, to provide information about new products, product surveys and for internal marketing tasks in the scope required. Participation for users is voluntary. If you do not wish to take part, you can deregister from these services at any time. You can do this whilst using the services themselves or via email to the address stated on the site. We will then block your data for any further use. Our employees are obliged to keep your personal data confidential.

 **Security**

Schaeffler Automotive Aftermarket GmbH & Co. KG uses technical and organizational security measures in order to safeguard the data we receive from you against accidental or deliberate deletion, manipulation, loss, and against unauthorized persons accessing the information. These security measures are constantly developed to meet new technical standards.

Our websites may contain links to other external websites. Our data protection policy does not apply for these websites.

Should you have any questions about how your personal data is processed, any comments or complaints, or should you require further information, please do not hesitate to contact the company or the company data protection officer.

On request, Schaeffler Automotive Aftermarket GmbH & Co. KG or the company responsible can provide you with information on whether your personal data has been stored by us and if so, which data has been stored. You will find the relevant person to contact on the company’s website. .

Thomas Biedermann

Data Privacy Officer

Schaeffler AG

Industriestrasse 1-3

91074 Herzogenaurach

Federal Republic of Germany

Dataprivacy@schaeffler.com
